schmap.me 2009-06-18

# Schmap Privacy Policy

Schmap recognizes and respects your desire for privacy. Please read the following provisions to learn more about Schmap's privacy policy.

  1. ### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Schmap does not collect your personal information. Personal information refers to information that is personally identifiable such as name, date of birth, address, or phone number.

  2. ### FINANCIAL INFORMATION

The Schmap Player and all of the Schmap Guides are free to end users and Schmap does not require end users to provide any financial information (credit card numbers, etc.). If anyone contacts you by email or otherwise claiming to represent Schmap and asks for your personal or financial information, please be aware that this is a fraudulent representation. You may report any such fraudulent activity to the Internet Fraud Complaint Center at <http://www.ic3.gov/>. 

  3. ### NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

Schmap may provide certain non-personally identifiable usage information to third parties, including information pertaining to the number of unique users of our destination/local guides. Schmap ascertains the number of unique users by assigning a unique player code to the Schmap Player on your computer at the point of installation. When You are connected to the Internet, the foregoing code will be communicated to Schmap's server(s) in order to collate aggregate usage statistics for our partners. The information gathered via the foregoing process may also be utilized by Schmap to inform users of updated product offerings and enable our advertisers to better customize their advertisements. 

  4. ### COOKIES

Schmap does not transfer any "cookies" to your computer. Cookies refer to small pieces of information that are transferred to your hard drive via your web browser to enable a web site to recognize your browser and for other tracking purposes. 

  5. ### FEEDBACK FORMS

Schmap does not require users to provide their name, email address, or any other personal information on our feedback forms. If you do provide any personal information to Schmap in the feedback forms we will use such information solely to make contact with you. 

  6. ### THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

For the convenience of our users, this website contains links to third party web sites that may be of interest. Schmap does not control how these third party web sites collect and use information about their users and therefore we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any such third party sites that you link to from this website . In order to review important information regarding safe Internet usage from the U.S. Federal Trade Commission, we encourage you to visit <http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menu-internet.htm>. 

  7. ### PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES

Schmap may update this policy from time to time by placing a notice on our web site. 

  8. ### TERMS OF USE

For more information on the terms and conditions that apply to the use of Schmap's web site, please review our Schmap Web Site Terms of Use. 

Effective Date: August 5, 2006
